RADOSLAV TOMAS

7 Callander road L6 8NT Liverpool 0751 444 3025 radoslav.tomas@gmail.com

noseyfish.co.uk radoslavtomas.com

SUMMARY

I am a data analyst and web developer living in Liverpool. For the last eight years, I have been working as an analyst for a company that monitors and analyses data from different media resources. In 2011 I started medan.sk site where my colleagues and I promote our work and write short analyses about the latest topics. This WordPress project has kindled my passion to become a web developer and I have since learned and used HTML5, CSS, jQuery and Angular JS to build web applications. Recently I've started with PHP and Python where I see a great opportunity for me to build applications that connect my two main interests – data and web developing. I am interested a job where I can share my skills, bring and learn something new and be part of a great team.

KEY SKILLS AND TOOLS

HTML5 (advanced)
CSS3 (advanced)
jQuery (intermediate)
Angular JS (intermediate)
PHP (basic)
Python (intermediate)

WordPress (intermediate)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web developer

July 2015 - present

I build web applications mostly on WordPress platform. I am also using technologies like jQuery, Angular JS and bit of PHP to create <u>static sites</u>.

Data Analyst - Newton Media

February 2009 – present

I produce analyses in a form of coverage reports (positive or negative articles, main topics, top media etc.) and quantitative inputs for marketers (advertising value equivalent, most influential authors etc.). In 2011 I created medan.sk site where my colleagues and I promote our work and write short analyses about the latest topics. I also wrote several analytical programs in Python that help with data processing.

Care and support worker - L'Arche Liverpool

March 2013 – present

I support people with learning disabilities. I assist them in the development of their independent living skills.

Find me on social media:











EDUCATION

Personal professional development

2012 - now

learn2code WebRebel course - HTML, CSS and JavaScript (Certified course by the

Ministry of Education in Slovak Republic)

WebRebel 2 course - PHP, SQL and Laravel (in progress)

Coursera Webdesign For Everybody (5-part course), Programming For Everybody

(Starting With Python), Python Data Structures, Using Databases With

Python, Using Python To Access Web Data)

Udemy Angular JS, The Complete Web developer Course, SQL Masterclass, Python

Programming

MA in Journalism - Comenius University, Slovakia

2006 - 2008

Modules Digital skills for journalists, Web design in on-line journalism, Data processing

BC in Marketing and PR - Comenius University, Slovakia

2003 - 2006

Modules Digital marketing strategies, Marketing and PR in the creative industries,

Research methods

INTERESTS

Running I have started to run two years ago, now I am training with some of my

friends for the half-marathon in Bratislava in April 2017.

Creative writing I have published three collections of poetry, which gained several prizes. I

also took part in many poetry readings in Slovakia and abroad.









